Guide to the Norman "Buddy" Baker Collection MSS.158
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Manuscript Scores by Buddy Baker
  - Kids is Kids - Autographs 531-TV, 17 Oct 1961; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 58)
    autograph black pencil 9 stave score on 18 stave yellow paper with red annotations; typed order of takes; photocopy piano conductor
    3129
    1A-7F(1)
  - Kids is Kids - Photocopy - piano conductor (Box 58)
  - Killers of the high country - Cougar - autograph - Cues 1A-3E, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 19)
    autograph black pencil six stave score on 12 stave yellow paper with red annotations
    5841
  - Kilroy 1, 3 TV 533, 21 Jan 1965; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 58)
    autograph black pencil 9 stave score on 18 stave yellow paper with red annotations;annotated order of takes and music breakdown (for Kit Carson)
    3291 TV
    1A-6D,13A-18X
  - King of the Grizzlies - Photocopy of piano conductor with annotations, 1969 Oct 13 -19; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 19)
    photocopy copyist's piano conductor;annotated form
    3448
    1B-11D2
  - Kit Carson and the mountain men - autographs - Cues 1B-8B [1B-12C], 1976 Ap 1; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 2 (Box 20)
    autograph black pencil short score on 12 stave yellow paper annotated in red and blue; annotated order of takes and music breakdown sheet
    3785
    1B-12C
  - Land Pavilion - American Folk Music - Manuscript short scores (Box 59)
  - Land Pavilion - American Folk Music -Autograph short scores I & II (Box 59)
  - Land Pavilion - Autograph full scores, undated (Box 59)
    autograph and orchestrator's short and full scores, black pencil on 8 and `16 stave yellow paper, annotated in red, blue and black; photocopy copyist short scores and lead sheet
    03J0803-000;03J1701;03J1702-003;51JA712-216
    fiddle,harmonium,6 and 12 string guitar, piano, accordian, drums, bass,banjo, pedal steel guitar
    Walt Disney Productions; Schaefer, Will; Bowden, Richard
  - Land Pavilion - Gentle on my mind/Everbody's Talkin' - photocopies, undated (Box 59)
    photocopy score
  - Land Pavilion - Kraft - Autograph - B Combo, 1980 Aug 7, 14; 8 (Box 59)
    autograph black pencil score on 12 stave yellow paper with black, red and blue annotations; typed and duplicated, annotated order of takes; full score; photocopies
    03J-0803-000;03J1502-003;51JA712-216; 03J1701-1702-003
  - Land Pavilion - Kraft - Autograph - C Combo (Box 59)
  - Land Pavilion - Listen to the Land - Autographs, 1980 May 7 (Box 59)
    autograph black pencil 4 and 6 stave score on 12 stave yellow paper with red and blue pencil annotations; photocopy copyist's lead sheets, annotated forms, notes
    03J0803.000
    A-H,J
    harmonium,fiddle,acoustic guitar, 12 str. Guitar, bass,banjo, piano, drums, tenor sax, 2 Bb tpt, elec and ped guitar, tbn,Fender bass,flute
  - Land Pavilion -Area Music (Box 59)
  - Liberty Square at Hall of Presidents - Autograph sketches (Box 60)
  - Liberty Square at Hall of Presidents - Autographs (Box 60)
  - Liberty Square at Hall of Presidents - Breakdown, etc., 1971 Jun 21-5,28;1977 Nov 16; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 7 (Box 60)
    autograph black pencil short scores on 12 stave yellow and white paper with red annotations; photocopy of cues from other productions; photocopy of short score; photocopies of printed music, manuscript notes; annotated Order of Takes music breakdown and orchestra recording schedule forms
    81-036-12-05;51-J-M143-022; 5910-003[film];0L04-002-15-622-02-12[phonograph]
    Unnumbered,1-12;F3,F4,F6-F10, 12 (1),F12-F14,S1-S4A-S4AA-S4AAA,S5-S6
  - Liberty Square at Hall of Presidents - Photocopies (Box 60)
  - Liberty Square at Hall of Presidents - Photocopy - copyist - piano conductor (Box 60)
  - Logos, Fanfares, Sketches, Misc., undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 60)
    autograph sketches, shorts scores; piano conductor
  - Lost Ones, The - Cues 2A-7C, 1973 Nov 19-21; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 3 (Box 21)
    autograph black pencil short score on 12 stave yellow paper with red,blue and purple annotations; annotated breakdown sheet, order of takes, orchestra schedule
    3622
    2A-12B
  - Magic Carpet 'Round the World - Order of takes 8, 7, 14 Dec 1972; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 8 (Box 61)
    annotated printed forms; autograph sketches on 12 stave white paper with blue and red annotations; manuscript full score;photocopy autograph sketches
    5925-003;5929-003
    1A-2H(1)
  - Magic Carpet 'Round the World -Autograph sketches - Cues 1A-2P, 2J(1)-2H(1) (Box 61)
  - Magic Carpet 'Round the World -Sketches - copy (Box 61)
  - Man is his worst enemy - Autograph 13, 1962/63 (Box 61)
    autograph black pencil 9 stave score with red annotations on 18 stave yellow paper; annotated piano conductor
    3177
    1A-2F(1)
  - Man is his worst enemy -Piano conductor (Box 61)
  - Mediterranean Cruise, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 61)
    3194
    4A-7MM
  - Meet the world - Tokyo - Photocopy - Piano Conductor (Box 22)
  - Meet the world - Tokyo - Photocopy full score, photocopy leadsheets, memo, 1961 Aug 3; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 8 (Box 22)
    photocopy full score, leadsheets;typed memo
    51-TBC01 BA
  - Meet the World - Tokyo - Script, etc., 1981 Ap 6, Sep 14, Nov 23; Sherman, Richard M., 1928-; Sherman, Robert B. (Box 22)
    copy typed script
    Sherman, Richard M., 1928-; Walt Disney Productions
  - Meet the world Tokyo - Autograph cues 1A-Star I-II, undated (Box 22)
    autograph black pencil short score on 12 stave yellow paper with red annotations interspersed with photocopy copyist's short score;photocopy copyist short score labelled Master rhythm and vocal lead; photocopy copyist short score
    5910-011;5950-011;03-J.1719.003;03-J-1719-004
    1A-4E,Star I-II
    Debney, John; Oldfield, Alan; Walt Disney Productions
  - Meet the world Tokyo - Script, etc., 1982 Aug 6; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 22)
    photocopy typed script; manuscript notes
  - Meet the world Tokyo - World showcase Japan - copyist short scores, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 22)
    photocopy copyist short score
    5910-042;5950.011;03-J-1719-003;03-J-1719-004
    1-4E
  - Meet the world Tokyo - World showcase Japan - script, notes (Box 22)
  - Menace on the Mountain, 1970 Jan 27-29; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 22)
    autograph black pencil short score on 12 stave white paper with red annotations; annotated order of takes, orchestra recording schedule
    3537
    1A-10D
  - Mexican Pavilion - Printed music, Map of park, Autograph pencil score, Photocopy full score, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 61)
    printed music, map of park, autograph pencil score, photocopy full score
    C304-002-16-622-03-12-TV
  - Mickey Mouse Theater - Main - Autograph score, music breakdown (Box 87)
  - Mickey Mouse Theater - Preshow - Autographs, piano conductor, 9-13 Nov 1970; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 3 (Box 87)
    annotated music breakdown,orchestra schedule; autograph black pencil 9 stave score on 18 stave yellow paper with red annotations
    5910-005;C304-002-15-622-03-12-TV
    A-Y,2alt,2(1-3);1-20v
  - Mickey Mouse Theater - Preshow - photocopy - score (Box 87)
  - Mickey's Christmas Carol (printed), undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 8 (Box 23)
    printed for use as production activity with guide and singer's edititon pak.
  - Mickey's Home Movies - Autograph (Box 62)
  - Mickey's Home Movies - Music Breakdown, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 6 (Box 62)
    annotated forms; autograph black pencil condensed score on 12 stave yellow paper with red, blue and green annotations; photocopy piano conductor score
    5910-020;5901-028;5910-020
    1A-2N,BB
  - Mickey's Home Movies - Piano conductor (Box 62)
  - Million Dollar Duck - Autograph 28, 1971 Mar 9, 11, 12; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 23)
    autograph black pencil short score on 12 stave white paper with red annotations;annotated breakdown sheets, order of takes, orchestra rehearsal; typed synopsis for publicity
    0111
    X,1A-10G1
  - Million Dollar Duck - Breakdown sheets - publicity (Box 23)
  - Minado the Wolverine - Autograph - Cue 1A-3F, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 62)
    1A-6X
  - Mountain born - Autograph (Box 23)
  - Mountain born - Breakdown sheet, etc, Autograph lead sheets, 1971 Nov 3-4 (Box 23)
    autograph black pencil short score on 12 stave white paper with red annotations;annotated breakdown sheets, order of takes, orchestral rehearsal;autograph black pencil lead sheets, photocopies of song by Sam Austin
    3586
    1B-6G1
    Walt Disney Productions; Austin, Sam
  - My dog the thief - A Combo, 1969 Jun 16-20, 23-27 (Box 23)
    autograph black pencil short score on 12 stave white paper with red and black annotations; autograph lead sheet; annotated breakdown, order of takes and orchestra recording forms; photocopies copyist vocal scores
    3465
    1Av-12B, Unnumbered
    Walt Disney Productions; Marks; Gilkyson, Terry
  - My dog the thief - B Combo (Box 23)
  - Mzee Simba - Autographs, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 23)
    autograph black pencil short score on 12 stave yellow paper with red, green and blue annotations
    3822
    1A-6E
  - Napoleon and Samantha - Autograph 14, 1972 Jan 19-21; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 24)
    autograph black pencil short score on 12 stave white paper with red annotations; one autograph sketch for cue 4B1;annotated music breaks downs, order of takes, orchestra recording schedule
    3598
    X-10D
  - Nashville Coyote - Autograph sketches, 1970 Oct 2, 1972 Feb 25; 5 (Box 24)
    photocopies copyist lead sheets; annotated music breakdown sheets; typed scripts
    3574
    Speirs, Jack; Walt Disney Productions
  - Nashville Coyote - Autograph sketches - short score, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 24)
    autograph black pencil sketches on 10 and 12 stave white and yellow paper;autograph black pencil short score on 12 stave white paper with red, green and black annotations; photocopy vocal parts short score
    1A-6K
  - Nashville Coyote - Photocopies - Short score (Box 24)
  - Nashville Coyote - Scripts, lead sheet, music breakdown (Box 24)
  - New York News, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 27)
    autograph and piano conductor
    8244-104
  - No deposit, no return - autographs, 1975 Dec 4-5, 8-9; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 4 (Box 25)
    autograph black pencil short score on 12 stave yellow paper with red annotations;annotated music breakdown, order of takes and orchestral recording schedule; notes
    0144
    1A-13E2
  - No deposit, no return - autographs - Cues 8A-13E (Box 25)
  - No deposit, no return - photocopies - copyist short score (Box 25)
  - No deposit, no return -music breakdown - Cues 1A-7E (Box 25)
  - Not So Lonely Lighthouse Keeper - copyist short score (Box 63)
  - Not So Lonely Lighthouse Keeper Cue 1A-1K - Full Score {!A - 6L inclusive], 1967 Aug 1-2; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 6 (Box 63)
    Autograph black pencil full score on 15 stave yellow paper with red and blue annotations; photocopy copyist short score, annotated in red; annotated order of takes and orchestra recording schedule
    3370
    1A-6L
    fl,pic,ob,Enghn,clars,bassclar,bsn,tpts,tbns,Frhns,strings,harp,vocal or special,piano, perc
  - One Day at Teton Marsh - Autograph score Cues 1X-3G, 3A-6D, 1964 Jun 5; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 5 (Box 64)
    autograph black pencil 9 stave score on 18 stave yellow paper with red, annotations; photocopy copyist piano conductor short score, annotated in red pencil; typescript
    1788
  - One Day at Teton Marsh - copyist short score (Box 64)
  - One Day at Teton Marsh - photocopy - script (Box 64)
  - One Day on Beetle Rock, 1967 Oct 3-4, 12 Aug; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 25)
    photocopy copyist piano conductor short score; annotated forms
    3426
  - One for the Road - Harry James autograph score and manuscript parts, 1994 Dec 2; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 64)
    autograph black pencil full and concert scores on 12 and 21 stave white and yellow paper annotated in red and blue;manuscript parts
    515;1590
    2altosax,2tensax,2clar.,baritone, 5 tpt, 3 tbn,drums, guitar, piano, bass
  - One for the Road - Photocopies - score and parts (Box 64)
  - Open Winter, 1976 Aug 26-27; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 5 (Box 26)
    autograph black pencil short score on 12 stave yellow paper with red, blue and green annotations; annotated order of takes, orchestra recording schedule
    3796
    1A-12D
  - Pearl Bailey - Sketches - 1 & 2, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 88)
    autograph black pencil short score on white and yellow 12 stave paper with red and purple annotations; photocopies of printed and ms. Music
    Bess;The way we were;Memories of you;What a wonderful thing is me;As long as he needs me; Where is love;Parade;Evergreen
  - Pearl Bailey - Two in love, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 4 (Box 88)
    photocopy of autograph full score
    Out of this world;Lonesome;Mirror on Water;Be my pretty flower;Love me forever;Dancing on a moonbeam;Can this be true;Don't be afraid to love me
  - Pond, The, 1975 Aug 11-15; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 26)
    autograph black pencil short score on 12 stave yellow paper with red, green and blue annotations; annotated music break down sheets, order of takes and orchestra recording schedule, notes
    3737
    1B-12E, unnumbered
  - Puppetoon Movie - Annotated forms, notes, photocopies short score, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 6 (Box 89)
    autograph black pencil sketches, short and full scores on 12 and 33 stave yellow paper with red,green,black and blue annotations; manuscript notes, annotated music breakdown and order of takes; photocopies autograph short score
    1A-1U;8A-8K
  - Puppetoon Movie - Autograph full score Cues 1A-1T, 8A-8K (Box 89)
  - Puppetoon Movie - Autograph short score Cues 1A-1U, 8A-8K (Box 89)
  - Puppetoon Movie - Autograph sketches (Box 89)
  - Raccoon Dog, The, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 26)
    autograph black pencil 6 stave score on 12 stave yellow paper with red annotations
    1A-3H
  - Radio City Music Hall, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 26)
    copyist piano conductor short score; photocopies orchestral parts
  - Rag, a bone, a box of junk, A - Autograph, 1964 Aug 21; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 65)
    autograph black pencil full score 18 staves with red annotations; photocopy copyist short score; annotated order of takes
    3280
    1B-6A
  - Rag, a bone, a box of junk, A - Full score - Cues 1A-6F (Box 65)
  - Rag, a bone, a box of Junk, A - Order of takes, 21 Aug 1964; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 6 (Box 65)
    typescript order of takes; annotated piano conductor; autograph black pencil 9 stave score on 18 stave yellow paper with red annotations
    1A-6A
  - Rag, a bone, a box of junk, A - Piano conductor (Box 65)
  - Rascal, 1969 Mar 10-14; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 26)
    autograph black pencil short score on 12 stave white paper with red and turquoise annotations; annotated music breadown sheets, orchestra recording schedule
    0104
    1X-11A
  - Return of the Big Cat - Autographs, 1974 Aug 19; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 27)
    autograph black pencil short score on 12 stave yellow paper with red, blue and green annotations; annotated forms
    3600
  - Run Cougar Run - Autograph - short scores (Box 27)
  - Run Cougar Run - Autograph sketches, breakdown, script, etc., 1972 June 12, 14, July 6 (Box 27)
    autograph black pencil short score on 12 stave white paper with red annotations;photocopy copyist piano conductor short score
    3557
    1X-12Gv
    Walt Disney Productions; Gilkyson, Terry
  - Run Cougar Run - Piano conductor - Photocopies (Box 27)
  - Run, light buck, run - Full score - Cue 1A-3E, 1965 Sep 17; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 65)
    autograph black pencil full score with red annotations, 18 staves; photocopy copyist short score; typed script
    3258
  - Run, light buck, run - Photocopy short score (Box 65)
  - Series TV, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 11+1 (Box 27)
    8202-004
    A,1-18B
  - Series TV - #8217, undated (Box 27)
    photocopy piano conductor short score
    8217-002
    1-8B
    Shows, Chas; Walt Disney Productions; Dodd, Jimmie, 1910-1964
  - Series TV - #8217 - 002-004 - Story of the Elephant, Story of the Camel, Story of the Beaver (Box 27)
  - Series TV - # 8244-107 - Cormorant fishing, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 27)
    photocopy piano conductor score
    8244-107
  - Series TV - #8202-004 - I'm no fool - Water safety (Box 27)
  - Series TV - #8202-03 I'm no fool - The Five Senses, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 27)
    8202-03
    A,1-16B
  - Series TV - #8203-02 I'm no fool, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 27)
    8203-02
    A,1-17B
  - Series TV - #8204-001, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 27)
    8204-001
    A,1-7
  - Series TV - #8244-014, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 27)
    8244-014
    1-8
  - Shaggy D.A. - M.P.1028 - Autographs, 1976 Oct 4-8 (Box 28)
    autograph black pencil short score on 12 stave yellow paper with red annotations; annotated orchestra recording schedule; photocopy copyist piano conductor short scores
    0155
    Unumbered, 1A-10G
    Sheets, Walter; McKinley, Richard M.; Walt Disney Productions
  - Shaggy D.A. - M.P.1028 - Photocopies (Box 28)
  - Silver Fox and Sam Davenport, The - Autograph condensed score Cues 1A-6E (Box 66)
    autograph condensed score
  - Sinbad - Autograph Full Score - 2,3 (Box 90)
  - Sinbad - Autograph score 1, 2, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 8 (Box 90)
    autograph black pencil condensed score on 18 stave white paper with red annotations; photocopy condensed score; black pencil full score on 33 stave light yellow paper with red annotations; photocopies, reduced, full score
  - Sinbad - Cue Sheet, Recording script (Box 91)
  - Sinbad - Floor Plan (Box 91)
  - Sinbad - Instrumental parts (Box 91)
  - Sinbad - Master Timings (Box 91)
  - Sinbad - Photocopies Full Score 3, 1998 Mar 22; 7 (Box 91)
    autograph black pencil master timing sheets with green, red and purple annotations on 12 stave yellow paper; autograph black pencil sketches and scores on 12 and 18 stave yellow and white paper;typed music cue list, ms. Notes, script; scenery designs, floor plan
  - Sinbad - Scenery designs (Box 91)
  - Sinbad - Storm - Score, Autograph sketches, photocopy (Box 91)
  - Sleeping Beauty, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 3 (Box 28)
    photocopy of full score
    2082
    M-T-3A
  - Small world clock D.L., undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 66)
    autograph black pencil full score on 18 stave yellow paper with red annoations
    B-G,Source1-9
  - Solomon, the sea turtle - Autographs, forms, etc., 1968 Feb 25, Mar 25, Sep 26; 5 (Box 29)
    autograph black pencil vocal short score on 10 and 12 stave white and yellow paper with red annotations; annotated orchestra recording form, typed lyrics, photocopy full score Stardust
    3460
    Vocal lead, 1A-6Gv1
    Marks; Walt Disney Productions; Thomas, Sam
  - Solomon, the sea turtle - Piano conductor - photocopies (Box 29)
  - Sonoton Library Cues - Parts (Box 66)
  - Sonoton Library Cues - Scores, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 7 (Box 66)
    photocopies of full score and parts
    Dance of the Lights;Mystery Land;Stalking; Torment
    Walt Disney Productions; Narholz, Gregor
  - Space mountain (R.C.A.) W. D. W. - Annotated forms, notes, etc., 1974 Jun 6, Oct 7-8, Sep 12; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 29)
    autograph black pencil and black ink short score on 10 and 12 stave yellow paper with red and green annotations;photocopy of copyist piano conductor short score; annotated music breakdown, orchestra recording schedule, typed script, highlighted cue sheet, photocopy choral arrangement of "Here's to the future and you"
    J0666-001
    1v-6A5
    Walt Disney Productions; Atencio, X.; Hammack, Bobby
  - Space mountain (R.C.A.) W. D. W. - Lead sheets and short score (Box 29)
  - Space mountain (R.C.A.) W. D. W. - Photocopies - piano conductor (Box 29)
  - Spanish Dancers (Von Drake in Spain) - TV554, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 66)
    autograph black pencil full score on 18 stave yellow paper with red and blue annotations
    3052
    1A-7D
  - Stardust - Autograph full score/photocopy short score, 2 (Box 92)
    autograph full score on 33 staves with red annotations; photocopies 7 stave score;printed full score and orchestral parts
    2fl,2ob,2cl,3tpt,3tbn,tuba,bells,bives,perc,solo Ctpt,guitar,celeste,harp,strings,basscl,2bsn,4hn
  - Stardust - Printed scores and parts (Box 92)
  - Summer magic - Annotated photocopy (Box 30)
  - Summer magic - Autographs, 1962 Feb 27; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 30)
    autograph black pencil vocal score with red annotations; annotated copyist short and vocal scores incomplete; annotated complete piano conductor short score
    2160
  - Summer magic - piano conductor - photocopy (Box 30)
  - Summer magic - piano conductor - vocal cues (Box 30)
  - Superdad - Son-in-law for Charlie McReady - Autographs, 1973 Jul 9-13; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 4 (Box 30)
    autograph black pencil short score on 12 stave yellow paper with red annotations; annotated breakdown sheets, orchestra recording schedule
    0119
    1XY -10Av1
  - Tale of two critters - Autographs, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 31)
    autograph black pencil short score on 12 stave yellow paper with red, green and blue annotations; photocopy copyist's piano conductor short score
    3795
    1BV-6E
  - Tale of two critters - Piano conductor - photocopy (Box 31)
  - Texas John Slaughter - Autographs - TV560, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 4 (Box 31)
    3131
    1C-6E
  - Texas John Slaughter 2 - Autographs - TV 560, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 31)
    5819
  - Tiger walks - Annotated forms, Theme (autograph and photocopy), 1963 Nov 26-27; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 4 (Box 67)
    autograph black pencil 9 stave score on 18 stave yellow paper with red annotations; anotated music breakdown and order of takes form; autograph and photocopy of black pencil theme on 12 stave white paper; photocopy copyist short score and vocal part
    2169
    1A-10F
  - Tiger walks - Autographs -Cues 1A-10F (Box 67)
  - Tiger walks - copyist short score (Box 67)
  - Toby Tyler - Cue 1A-4EE(1), undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 3 (Box 32)
    autograph black pencil 6 stave score on 12 stave yellow paper with red and green annotations
    5840
    1A-11DD
  - Tomorrow's child layout, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 33)
    autograph black pencil short score on 12 stave yellow paper with red annotations; photocopy of short score, notes
  - Treasure of Matecumbe - Annotated forms, photocopies parts, 1976 Mar 1-5, Ap 6,12,19, May 10-14, 17; 8 (Box 68)
    autograph black pencil short score on 12 stave yellow paper with red, green and blue annotations; annotated music breakdown, cue sheets, orchestra recording schedule; photocopies copyist short score; photocopies parts
    0145
    1A-12E
    Tatum, W.; Walt Disney Productions
  - Treasure of Matecumbe - Autograph - Cues 1A-12E (Box 68)
  - Treasure of Matecumbe - copyist short score (Box 68)
  - Tres Cochinitos, Los - Autograph sketch and short score, undated; Sherman, Robert B. (Box 68)
    autograph black pencil 4 stave sketch on 8 stave white paper; autograph black pencil short score on 12 stave white paper with red annotations; annotated breakdown sheet; photocopy copyist short score
    5954-039;2198;2189
    Unnumbered, 1A-H
    Sherman, Richard M., 1928-; Walt Disney Productions; Elliott, Jack, 1927-2001
  - Tres Cochinitos, Los - copyist short score and photocopies (Box 68)
  - Unidentified - EPS 1(1) - 12(4) - Autographs, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 37)
    autograph black pencil short score on 12 stave yellow paper with red and blue annotations
    EPS 1(1) -12(4)